Hi there. Firstly, thank you for booking
this call, and congratulations.
So before we jump into this, it is my job to make
sure you do your research and your diligence.
If you're anything like me and spend a ton of time on your
business, you'll know a lot of that time is wasted.
And maybe that has led you to not trust
in individuals or agencies.
So let me tell you a little bit about me,
the business and what you can expect.
I've generated over 220 million rand for clients,
and I've done over 1000 of these calls
with business owners just like you.
So I've compiled all the concerns and all the
questions in little 30 second snippets.
So just scroll down below.
They are on 1.5 times speed,
so you can get through them real quick and have a
look at every single question and concern.
I'm really excited to see you on the other side.